Fred Rochlin papers, 1694-2002 (bulk 1880-1930),
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 4: Research Files, 1694-2001 (bulk 1880-1930), 25 linear ft.
  - Subseries: Arizona, 1694-2001
    - Korrick, Charles and Abe. 1882-1972 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Korrick, Sam. 1889-1901 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Koshlnd, William and Henry. 1886-1896 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - La Paz. 1850-1880 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Lachman, Henry. 1870-1871 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Lantin, Max. 1874-1901 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Latz, John. 1880-1928 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Lazard, Alphonse. 1832-1895 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Leeker, Sam. 1876-1976 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Lesinsky, Charles. 1863-1948 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Lesinsky, Charles III. 1907-1981 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Lesinsky- Freudenthal- Solomon Family. 1869-1921 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Lesinsky, Henry. 1867-1924 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Lesinsky Mines. 1870-1885 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Letterhead. 1880-1910 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Levi, Herman, Company. 1890-1891 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Levin, Alexander. 1833-1902 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Levin, Ernest. 1985 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Levin Family. 1878-1981 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Levin, Henry. 1868-1927 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Levy, Ben. 1882-1972 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Levy, David. 1876-1903 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Levy Department Store. 1903-1972 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Levy Family. 1878-1969 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Levy, Felix. 1857-1925 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Levy Gabe. (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Levy, Henry. 1884-1969 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Levy, Isaac. 1844-1899 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Levy, Jim. 1842-1882 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Levy, Leon. 1913-1973 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Levy, Moses. 1886 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Levy, M.G. 1859-1941 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Levy, Nathan. 1895-1920 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Lewis, Sol, National Bank of Arizona. 1877-1981 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Lieberman, Julius. 1859-1889 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Loeb, David. 1879-1951 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Lohn, A.W. 1863-1956 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Lulley, Emanuel. 1809-1895 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Lulley- Ezekiels Family. 1809-1928 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Lulley Family. 1809-1974 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Lulley, John. 1845-1915 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Lulley, Mark. 1857-1915 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Lulley Mines. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Lulley, Mose. 1883 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Lyon, Abraham. 1861-1869 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Lyon, Isaac. 1846-1889 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Maier, Bernhard. 1869 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Manfeld, Jacob Samuel. 1832-1894 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Mansfeld, Samuel Jacob. 1881 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Marcus, Sam. (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Marcus, Josephine and Wyatt Earp. 1848-1944 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Marks, Barnett Ellis and Wife. 1880 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Marks, Emil. 1864 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Marks, Henry. 1863-1870 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Marks, Jake. 1833-1907 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Mashbir, Frieda. 1925 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - McKinney's Pacific Coast Directory. 1883-1884 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Meier, J.A. 1860-1866 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Mendelowitz Family. 1880-1930 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Michelsen, George. 1866-1917 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Morenci, AZ. 1870-1890 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Moses, J.A. 1827-1893 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Murstein, Pearl Rosenthal. 1908-1988 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Negri, Sam. 1980-1989 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Nineteenth Century Map. 1877 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Newman, John B. (Black Jack). 1862-1928 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Newman, Moses. 1862-1904 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Nogales. 1880-1930 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Nogales, Jewish Cemetery. 1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Nogales "Strip" Claims and Reimbursement. 1939 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Oberfelder and Co. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Orndoff, Richard E. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Peck, Arthur. 1845-1939 (Box 18, Folder 6-9)
    - Peterson, Cele. 1974 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Pima County- Territorial Marriages. 1871-1912 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Pimera Alta Historical Society. 1948-1990 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
    - Pioneers. 1850-1900 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Portrait and Biographical Record of Arizona, Index. 1901 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Posner, Philip. 1880-1962 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Prescott. 1986 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
    - Prescott, Early Jewish Settlers. 1863-1880 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Price, Israel. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Rattner, Leon. 1900-1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Ready, Alma- Pimera Alta Historical Society Research Library. 1981 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Related Family in Mexico and New Mexico. 1880-1975 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Reznikov, Dr. Anna. 1917-1918 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Rice, Gorge Graham. (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Rochlin, Claire. (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Ronstadt, Fred. 1868-1954 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Rosen Family. 1988 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Rosenberg, Arthur S. 1916-1986 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Rosenberg, Mrs. Ana L. 1880-1966 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Rosenberg, Mrs. Morris. 1855-1930 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Rosenberg, Stella. 1969 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Rosenberg, William. 1863-1955 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Rosenfeld, Fred William. 1895 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Rosenstern, Chester and Louis. 1868-1923 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Rosenzweig, Harry. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Roth, Paul N. 1880-1890 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Sachs, Wolf. 1853 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Salmon Family. 1864-1903 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Salzman, Max. 1885-1913 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Samuels, Samuel. 1878-1934 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Santa Cruz County. 1860-1980 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schaben, Henry. 1880-1883 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Scharff, Alvin F. 1967 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Schuckmann, William. 1894-1901 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Schuster, A. and B. 1864-1924 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Schuster Family. 1880-1966 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Schuster and Wetzler Family. 1880-1920 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Schutz Family. 1875-1908 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Schwartz, Solomon J. 1884 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Seligman, Jesse. 1849-1894 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Seligman Post Office. 1886-1964 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Seligman and the Railroads. 1886-1986 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Seligman, C. and Co. 1886 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Sandoval, P. 1884-1900 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Sharfman, Rabbi I. Harold. 1970 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Show Low History. 1869-1930 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Simonon, Georges. 1949-1977 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Smith, Reverend O.A. 1920-1960 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Snyder, Fred. 1884-1934 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Solomon Family. 1841-1977 (Box 20, Folder 26-27)
    - Solomon, I.E. 1841-1930 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Solomon, Lili. 1961 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Solomon- Wickersham Lawsuits. 1909-1912 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Solomonville. 1876-1960 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Southern Arizona Bank and Trust. 1903-1970 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Spitalny Family. 1890-1899 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Steinfeld, Albert and Wife. 1854-1935 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Steinfeld, Harold. 1888-1970 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Steinfeld Family. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Steinfeld Store. 1854-1954 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Strauss, Charles. 1840-1892 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Temple Emanuel. 1910-1982 (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
    - Tombstone. 1880-1984 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Tombstone, Boothill Cemetery. 1880-1984 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Tubac. 1857-1949 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Tucson, History. 1694-1970 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - United Synagogue Youth. 1972 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - United States Military Academy Library. 1921 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Wertheimer, Aaron. 1831-1874 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Wetzler, J. Charlie. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Wienberg and Brown Family. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Wittig, Ed. 1865-1934 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Wollenberg, Louis. 1859-1869 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Wollenberg Family. 1878-1906 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Wormser, Michael. 1827-1898 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Yellow Jacket Mine. 1877-1889 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Yuma. 1858-1939 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Zeckendorf, Aaron. 1835-1872 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Zeckendorf, Mrs. Arthur. 1933-1935 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Zeckengorf Family. 1838-1954 (Box 22, Folder 10-11)
    - Zeckendorf, Julia. 1935 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Zeckendorf, Louis. 1838-1901 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Zeckendorf, Store. 1874-1878 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Zeckendorf, William. 1842-1906 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Zeckendorf, William II. 1905-1976 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Zeckendorf, W.- J Frank and Co. 1878 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Subseries: California, 1807-1994
    - Fleishhacker, Delia and Aaron. (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Frankfort, Jacob. 1841 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Franklin Brothers. 1820-1879 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Ganz, Emil and Judge Wollenberg. (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Greene, Lauren 1980s-1994 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Israel, Robert. 1849-1880 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Jewish Community Library of Los Angeles- Bisno Archives. 1972-1976 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Jewish Genealogical Society of Los Angeles. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Koshland Family. 1825-1906 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Lazard Freres. 1876-1979 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Lazard, Solomon. 1826 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Mannassee Family. 1850-1938 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Mannassee, Joseph and Hannah (Schriller). 1832-1913 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Rose, Louis. 1807-1888 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - San Bernadino Jewish Community. 1860-1935 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - San Diego, Beth Israel. 1876-1919 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - San Diego, Early Jews. 1850-1880 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - San Francisco Jewish Cemeteries. 1981 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Southern California Jewish Historical Society. 1985-1988 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Southern Pacific Railroad Papers. 1882-1898 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Stern, Dr. Norton. 1966 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Varney, Ginger. 1984 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Weinberger, Jacob. 1882-1974 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Western Jewish History Center. 1968-1986 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Western Jewish Historical Quarterly. 1967-1985 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Wolf, Hyman. 1889-1932 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Subseries: Colorado, 1980-1988
    - Colorado Jewish History: A Guide for Teachers. 1983 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Rocky Mountain Chai. 1981-1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Rocky Mountain Jewish Historical Society. 1980-1985 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Subseries: General, 1882-2001
    - California Museum of Photography. 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - El Paso Book Bindery. 1985 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Lehman, Marshall. 1980-1984 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Plotkin, Sylvia. 1882 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Scaroni, Hank. 1995 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Wyner, Justin. 2001 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Subseries: Mexico, 1849-1989
    - Arizona and Mexico. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Barsky Family. 1989 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Business and Professional Listings. 1931 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - David, Joseph. 1908 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - El Estado de Sonora, Mexico: Sus Industrias Comerciales, Mineras y Manufactureras. 1897 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Goldsmith, Ben. 1899 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Latz and Faeber Family. 1849-1920 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Latz, Miguel. 1849-1920 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Nogales, Sonora. 1849-1960 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Punitive Expedition. 1916 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Sandoval, P. 1884 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Sonora and Arizona. 1849-1934 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Sonora, Mexico. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Sonora Newspapers. 1872-1937 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Tostado, Pascual Alverez- Taxes and Business. 1913-1922 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Subseries: New Mexico, 1810-1992
    - Abraham Family. 1824-1932 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Albuquerque. (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Beach, Williams- Photo Captions. (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Centennial Celebration. 1949 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Cohen, Isaac N. 1865-1893 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Cohen, Isaac, Business Listings, Silver City. 1875-1930 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - German Jew and the Commercial Revolution in the Territorial New Mexico. 1850-1900 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Gottlieb Family. 1810-1990 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Gusdorf, Alexander. 1848-1923 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Ilfeld- Nordhaus Family. 1740-1960 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Jaffe-Prager Family. 1875-1900 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Jewish and German Pioneers. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Klein, Sam. 1949 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Kohn, Yetta Goldsmith. 1843-1917 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Lidauer, Sigmund and Family; Rauel Bros. Wormser Store. 1869-1977 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Lowenstein, Benjamin and Obermayer, Hermann. 1959-1996 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Myer Family. 1907-1908 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - New Mexico Art Colony: Jewish Artists and Patrons 1875-1960 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - New Mexico Historical Society. 1990-1996 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - New Mexico Personalities. 1880-1930 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Pioneer Jews of Albuquerque. 1840-1920 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Research Trip. 1984 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Research Trip New Mexico and Colorado. 1981 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Rio Grande Historical Archives- Photographs. (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Sachs Family, and Simon Neustadt, and Co. 1867-1980 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Silver City. 1870-1920 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Staten, Charna and Williams, Francis. 1940-1988 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Tumacari. 1907-1908 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Waxman Family. 1913-1992 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Subseries: Photographic Research, 1868-1991
    - Borderlands Photographs. 1880-1930 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Bray, Mayfield. 1972 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Elliot, L.B. 1917-1923 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Ezekiels Family. 1991 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Herrera, Rachel mix Collection. 1893-1913 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Horne, W.H.- El Paso, Texas. 1981 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Mexican and U.S. Photographs. 1868-1930 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Rochlin, Fred Collection- Nogales. 1880-1940 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Spude, Robert. 1900-1910 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Subseries: Texas, 1813-1994
    - 100 Years of Jewry in San Antonio. 1813-1920 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Cattle Brands. 1850-1900 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Corsicana. 1893-1984 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Fair (Fchr) Family. 1830-1994 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Jewish Community. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Jewish Historical Society and Dallas Jewish Archives. 1984-1989 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Mexico Border. (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - El Paso, Ciudad Juarez and Chihuahua. 1984 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Subseries: Washington, 1858-1995
    - no title 1885-1895 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Bridge Family. 1896-1995 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Port Townsend. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Rothschild Family. 1858-1974 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Seattle. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Waterman and Katz Family. 1859-1920 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Subseries: West, 1808-1987
    - Cattlemen in the West. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Explorations and Surveys. 1853-1856 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Hawaii. 1979 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Hilton Sketches. 1858-1870 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Idaho and Wyoming 1800-1920 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - International Survey of Jewish Monuments. 1985-1987 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Jewish Intermarriage in the American West. 1875-1975 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Jews in the West. 1850-1920 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Jews in the West, Bibliography. (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Lasaur Brothers and the Sandbar Saloon. 1887-1900 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Maps. (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Nebraska. 1890-1986 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Nevada Census. 1870-1880 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Official Surveys of the United States Before USGS of 1879. 1830-1879 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Peddlers and Merchants. 1850-1880 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Philipson, Jacob. 1808-1858 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Reinhart Store. 1868 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Rancho San Jose de Buenos Ayres. 1979 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Rocky Mountain Jewish Historical Society Conference. (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Settlements in Western Canada. 1860-1920 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Silko, Leslie Marmon. 1981-1984 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Society of Southwestern Authors. 1985 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Wroth Photograph Collection. 1883-1924 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Zion in America. 1881-1916 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Zionism and Anti-Zionism in the West: The San Francisco Experience. 1918-1968 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Series 5: Photograph Files, 1850-1986, 19.75 linear ft.
  Photograph Files contain nine subseries. Subseries: Borderlands (1890-1960) contains images of the border region of Arizona and Mexico. Subseries: Copy Prints (1860-1986) contain images of individuals and places in the Southwest. Subseries: Military (1940-1986) contains images of WWII military personnel, equipment, engagement, reunions, and Fred Rochlin during his term of service. Subseries: Miscellaneous Arizona and the Southwest (1880-1945) contains images of people and places throughout the West. Subseries: Nogales (1850-1970) contains images of individuals, places and events in Nogales, AZ. Subseries: Western Jews (1875-1950) contains images of early Jewish pioneers in the West. Subseries: Exhibit Photographs (1868-1929) contains matted images of Jewish individuals, families, and businesses in the southwest. Subseries: Oversize Photographs (1868-1945) contains images of various people and places. Subseries: Panoramas (1916) contains panoramic photographs of the army and their camps during the Mexican Punitive Expedition.
  - Subseries: Borderlands, 1890-1960
    - Arizona, Miscellaneous Cities. 1900-1920 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Arizona, Nogales. 1890-1970 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Arizona, U.S. Troops. 1914-1918 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Mexico, Cananea, Sonora. 1900-1960 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Mexico, Mexican Troops. 1900-1920 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Mexico, Nogales, Sonora. 1891-1930 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Mexico, Sonora, Miscellaneous Cities. 1900-1910 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified Persons. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified Places. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Subseries: Copy Prints, 1860-1986
    - AJHS Annual Conference. 1985 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Baker, Marion- Book Plate. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Bernalillo Mercantile Co.- Alburquerque, New Mexico. 1920-1930 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Colorado. 1885-1925 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Cover Sheet Proofs for Rochlin Photograph Collection. 1984 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Ephriam, Leopold- Nogales, Arizona. 1880-1900 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Frashier Collection- Nogales, Arizona and Sonora. 1930-1939 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Friedman, Sam- Benson, Arizona. 1880-1902 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Goldbaum, Julius- Whisky Bottle Labels. (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Goldbaum, Marcus and Julius- Tucson, Arizona. (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Chernin, Homer- Nogales, Arizona. 1920-1930 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Isaacson, Jacob- Nogales, Arizona. 1880 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Isaacson, John and Sons. 1969 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, Charles G.- Views of the Arizona and the Colorado River. 1868 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Latz- Faerber. 1850-1950 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Levy, Dave- Nogales, Arizona. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Lulley Family- Tombstone. 1986 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Lully, Mose- Tucson, Arizona. 1883 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous- Arizona. 1860-1910 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous- Nogales. 1880-1955 (Box 30, Folder 9-10)
    - Nogales. 1890-1900 (Box 30, Folder 11-12)
    - Nogales Photograph Exhibit. 1890-1985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Railroads- Yuma, Arizona. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Rosenberg, William- Tubac, Arizona. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - San Diego County. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Southwest and Mexican Revolution. 1890-1920 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Texas. 1889-1910 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Tumacacori Mission Slides. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Subseries: Military, 1940-1986
    - 456th Bomb Group, 1986 Reunion. 1986 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Aircraft. 1940-1949 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets. 1940-1949 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - People. 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Rochlin, Fred. 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Subseries: Miscellaneous Arizona and the Southwest, 1880-1945
    - Arizona, Various Cities. 1880-1940 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Cananea, Sonora, Mexico. 1900 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Langpaap, Eleanor Collection- Tombstone, Arizona. 1900-1920 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - National Archives Photos, Nogales, Arizona. 1916-1917 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - New Mexico, Various Cities. 1880-1910 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Nogales, Arizona.. 1890-1930 (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
    - San Francisco, California. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Seattle, Washington. 1900 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Texas, Various Cities. 1900-1920 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - United States Army Troops on the Border. 1916-1945 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Unknown Places. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Various Portraits. 1870-1920 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Subseries: Nogales, 1850-1970
    - Nogales. 1850-1899 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Nogales. 1900-1930 (Box 33, Folder 1-4)
    - Aguilar Collection. 1920-1929 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Atlantic and Pacific Railroad Route. 1884 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Beach, William Y.- Arizona and New Mexico Scenes, Book 1. 1882-1883 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Beach, William Y.- Arizona and New Mexico Scenes, Book 2. 1882-1883 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Buehman Photographs. 1880-1905 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Cananea, Sonora, Mexico. 1920 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Century of Railroading. 1880-1943 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Cook, L.L. and Frasher Collections. 1936-1939 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Ekey, Ada Jones Collection- Book 1. 1915-1924 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Ekey, Ada Jones Collection- Book 2. 1915-1924 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Elloit, L.B. Collection. 1916-1918 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Herrera, Rachel Mix Collection. 1880-1915 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Mexican Revolution. 1900-1920 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Monarque, A. Collection. 1880-1930 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Naco. 1914-1930 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Santa Cruz County. 1850-1900 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Series, Book 1. 1890-1930 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Series, Book 2. 1913-1930 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Series, Book 3. 1917 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Series, Book 4. 1910-1925 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Series, Book 5. 1910-1920 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Series, Book 6. 1914-1970 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Series, Book 7. 1921 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Series, Book 8. 1914-1916 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Don Collection, Book 1. 1900-1920 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Don Collection, Book 2. 1900-1920 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Don Collection, Book 3. 1900-1920 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Temple Collection. 1900-1920 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Suberies: Western Jews, 1875-1950
    - Early Jewish Settlers of New Mexico Territory. 1890-1920 (Box 36, Folder 8-9)
    - Early Texas Jewish Settlers. 1880-1920 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Jews of Nogales. 1900-1950 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Jews of Sonora, Mexico. 1890-1910 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Pioneer Jews of Arizona- Book 1. 1880-1890 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Pioneer Jews of Arizona- Book 2. 1875-1900 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Pioneer Jews of Arizona- Book 3. 1880-1900 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Pioneer Jews of Arizona- Book 4. 1880-1910 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Subseries: Exhibit Photographs, 1868-1929
    - Railroad Depot, Solomonville, AZ. 1895 (Box 38)
    - Sam Katzenstein, Charleston, AZ. 1929 (Box 38)
    - Sam Katzenstein, La Paz, Mexico. 1929 (Box 38)
    - Sam Katzenstein's Store, Charleston, AZ. 1925-1929 (Box 38)
    - Isaac Levy Dry Goods Store, Yuma, AZ. 1896 (Box 38)